http://www.generallyawesome.com/privacy.html

Privacy Policy
www.GenerallyAwesome.com is not in the business of collecting personal data.
We collect personal data from visitors for 2 very specific purposes listed below, aside from which we do not otherwise collect personal data.
Personal data that we do collect is held private; www.GenerallyAwesome.com does not sell, trade, barter, or otherwise disseminate personal information to any third party.
Here are specific instances where data is collected:
1) E-mail addresses are collected from those visitors who request to be informed of content updates and offers from www.GenerallyAwesome.com.
This service is voluntary, and any e-mail address collected for this purpose is used solely for this purpose.
Those wishing to opt out are free to do so at any time by simply following the "unsubscribe" instructions at the bottom of every message.
2) Customer information is collected from individuals purchasing merchandise from www.GenerallyAwesome.com’s
store on PayPal and the store on www.CafePress.com
by each site directly.
The information is collected and used only for the purposes of collecting payments from and delivering goods to customers.
It is not revealed to any third parties at any time.
For more specific details on the privacy policies of our partners click on the desired company name: PayPal and www.CafePress.com.
During the process of delivering content to you, with the exception of the aforementioned cases listed above, www.GenerallyAwesome.com does not collect any personally identifiable information about you such as name, address, phone number, or e-mail address. However, www.GenerallyAwesome.com does obtain some types of non-personally identifiable information such as the Internet Service Provider you use to connect to the Internet, your browser type, or the type of computer operating system you use (Macintosh or Windows, for example). The information collected by www.GenerallyAwesome.com is used for the purpose of targeting content and optimizing site performance.
BACK
_____________________________________________
_______ "Occasionally lame, but generally awesome."________
____________________________________________
Home | Comics | Humor | Archive | Photos | Pirates | Store
All content ©www.GenerallyAwesome.com 2003-2004
Privacy | Disclaimer
